Guide to the Robert F. Curl Academic papers, 1953- 2012, bulk 1985-1993 MS 483
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IX: Research publications addendum, 1959-1997
  - 1970s
    - Infrared-Radio Frequency Double Resonance Observations of Pure Rotational Q-Branch Transitions of Methane, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave-infrared double resonance of CH4 using 3.39u He-Ne laser line, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave spectrum of 2-Nitrophenol: Structure of the Hydrogen Bond, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - High resolution obervation of microwave-optical double resonance in NO2, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Optical Double Resonance and Fluorescence Spectrum of NO2 Excited by the 4579 A Line of the Argon-Ion Laser, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Saturation Spectroscopy of BO2 at 5145A, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Chloromethyl Methyl Ether, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Silyl Methyl Ether, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Determination of Transition Moments from Power Saturation, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of 3,3-Epoxy-1-Butene, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Spectroscopy with Modulation Sidebands, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave optical double resonance spectrum of NH2. I. Ground State, 14N hyperfine coupling constants, and spin rotation constants, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Laser Excitation of the 5d2D5/2 Level of Cs during Collision with Rare Gas Atoms, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of NO2 in the v2=1 State, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Optical Double Resonance Observations of a Rotational Transition of NH2, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave optical double resonance spectrum of NH2. I. Ground state, 14N hyperfine coupling constants, and spin rotation constants, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Saturation Spectroscopy of NH2 using a CW Dye Laser, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Laser magnetic resonance spectrum of HCO on the D2O 108u laser line, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Study of the N2O3-H2O-HNO2 Equilibrium by Intensity Measurements in Microwave Spectroscopy, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - The Microwave Spectrum, Structure, Dipole Moment, and Internal Rotation of the Methyl Isocyanide-Borance Complex, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave optical double resonance spectrum of NH2. II. Collison-induced transitions in A2A, and observations of a new vibronic state, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave optical double resonance spectrum of NH2. III. 1H and 14N hyperfine coupling constants and spin rotation constants in X2B, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Hyperfine Structure in the A State of PH2 Arising from the Fermi Interaction of 31P, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave optical double resonance spectrum of NH2. IV. Observation of an unusual rotational transition in X2B, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave optical double resonance spectrum of NH2. V. Hyperfine structure of the u state, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave modulated saturation spectroscopy, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum, Structure, Dipole Moment, and Internal Rotation of cis-Azomethane, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Intermodulated fluorescence spectroscopy of BO2 using a stablized dye laser, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum, Dibole Moment, and Structure of 3-Aminopropanol, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - The Microwave Spectrum of Tertiarybutylisocyanide-Borane, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Erratum: Microwave modulated saturation spectroscopy, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1980s
    - Sensitivity enhancement of laser absorption spectroscopy by magnetic roation effect, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Chemiluminescent Reaction Channel Opened by Photo Absorption During Collision, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Microwave optical double resonance of NH2. VI. Ground state of NHD, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Observation of the 2P1/2-2P3/2 Transition of the Br Atom by Color Center Laser Spectroscopy, 1981 (Box 12, Episode 4)
    - Infrared Absorption Spectroscopy with Color Center Lasers, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - A determination of the spin-rotation parameters for NO2 in the X2A1 state by microwave-optical double resonance, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Color Center Lasers for High Resolution Spectroscopy, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Microwave optical double resonance spectrum of NH2. VII. Hyperfine coupling constants ..., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Infrared absorption spectrum of C2H radical with color center laser, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - A2II-... infrared electronic transtion of C2H, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Color Center Laser Spectroscopy of v1 + v2 + v3 of NO2 using Magnetic Rotation, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Photoexcitation of the NaKCI Reaction Complex, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Non-Linear Stark Polarization Spectroscopy, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Color Center Laser Kinetic Spectroscopy, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Kinetic Spectroscopy with the Color Center Laser, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Experimental Excitation of a Transition State in a Chemical Reaction, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - The OH Stretching Fundamental of Hydroxylamine, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Sensitivity improvement of tone-burst modulated spectroscopy with a color-center laser, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Rotational analysis of the A-X system of C2H, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Erratum: Rotational analysis of teh A-X system of C2H, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Semiconductor cluster beams: One and two color ionization studies of Six and Gex, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Magnetic Rotation Observation..., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - The Microwave and Far-Infrared Spectra of the SiH Radical, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Chemiluminescent Channels Opened by Photon Absorption During Reactive Collisions, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Color-center laser kinetic spectroscopy..., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Reactivity of Large Carbon Clusters;: Spheroidal Carbon Shells and Their Possible Relevance to the Formation and Morphology of Soot, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Studies of the NH2 + NO Reaction by Infrared Kinetic Spectroscopy, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Negative Carbon Cluster Ion Beams: New Evidence for the Special Nature of C60, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Observation of the laser-assisted reaction K + NaCl +hv ..., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Photodetachment and photofragmentation studies of semiconductor cluster anions, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - A Reply to "Magic Numbers in Cn..., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - The Formation of Long Carbon Chain Molecules during Laser Vaporization of Graphite, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Color center laser spectroscopy of vibrationally excited C2H, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Multiwavenumber linearized diode laser spectra by overlapping frequency scans, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Rate Constant Measurements of Reactions with C2H with..., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Color Center Laser Spectroscopy of C2H and C2D, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Photophysics of buckminsterfullerene and other carbon cluster ions, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Photodissociation of semiconductor positive cluster ions, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Infrared flash kinetic spectroscopy of HCO, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Probing C60, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Unbiased Least-Squares Fitting of Lower States, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Infrared Kinetic Sprectoscopy of C2H and C2D, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - The OH Stretching Fundamental of Methanol, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Reaction Mechanism of C2H + O2, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Infrared Spectroscopy of Jet-Cooled Transient Molecules, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1990s
    - Rate Constant Measurements of C2H with C2H6..., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Ammonia chemisorption on gallium arsenide clusters, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Thermal deNOx: no HNO at room temperature, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Photoexcitation spectra of transition region species in reactions of potassium with sodium halides, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Vibrational relaxation of acetylene produced by the photolysis of vinyl bromide, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - CW Difference Frequency Generation..., 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Infrared Flash Kinetic Spectroscopy of v2 of Ketenyl Radical, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pre-1990 Evidence for the Fullerene Proposal, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Acetylene combustion reactions..., 1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Rotationally resolved spectrum of the v1 CH stretch..., 1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - On the formation of the fullerenes, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - The v1 fundamental of HCCN: evidence for quasiliniearity, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Collapse and growth, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - The Reaction of NH2 with O, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Nonlinear Optics for High-Speed Electronics and Optical Frequency Conversion, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Rate Constant Measurement of the Recombination Reaction C3H3 + C3H3, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Quasi-linearity in HCCN..., 1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Propargyl from the Reaction of Singlet Methylene with Acetylene, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Role of Fine Structure States in a Chemical Reaction..., 1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Nobel lectures in chemistry, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Reaction of Cyanomethylene..., 1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Undated
    - Mass Spectrometric Studies of the Fullerenes (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Series X: Non-Rice Boards and Committees, 2000-2008
  - Committee on Human Rights of the National Academy of Sciences (NAS), National Academy of Engineering (NAE), and Institute of Medicine (IOE) (2001 - 2008)
    Contents
    Each of these files contains the agendas, minutes, membership information, financial reports, correspondence, and human rights case information from the biannual meeting of the Committe on Human Rights of the National Academy of Sciences (NAS), National Academy of Engineering (NAE), and the Institute of Medicine (IOM).
    - Biannual Meeting: October 2001 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Biannual Meeting: April 2003 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Biannual Meeting: October 2003 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Biannual Meeting: April 2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Biannual Meeting: May 2005 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Biannual Meeting: October 2005 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Biannual Meeting: April 2006 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Biannual Meeting: October 2006 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Biannual Meeting: May 2007 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Biannual Meeting: September 2007 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Biannual Meeting: April 2008 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - The Academy of Medicine, Engineering, and Science of Texas
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Feb. 2004 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Aug. 2004 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Aug. 2005 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Jan. 2006 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Feb. 2006 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Aug. 2006 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Aug. 2007 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Executive Director's Report: Aug. 2007 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - O'Donnell Awards Committee Papers: Aug. 2007 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Jan. 2008 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Board/Committee Papers: 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Board/Committee Papers: 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board, Advisory Committee on Research Projects, 2000-2008
    - ACORP: 2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - ACORP: 2001 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - ACORP: 2003 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - ACORP: 2004 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - ACORP: 2004 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - ACORP: 2004 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - ACORP: 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - ACORP: 2005 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - ACORP: 2006 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - ACORP: 2007 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - ACORP: 2007 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - ACORP: 2008 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Series XI: Addendum, 1953-2012
  - Subseries A: Correspondence
    - A (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Academie Europeene des Sciences (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - American... (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - American Academy of Arts Sciences (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - American Academy of University Professors (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - American Chemical Society (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - B (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Babu, Dr. Dinesh, K.V. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Baggott, Dr. James (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - British Columbia, University of (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Brookhaven National Laboratory (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Buckminster Fuller, Sadao and Zung Architects (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Burleigh Instruments, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - C (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - California, University of (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Camille Henry Dreyfus Foundation (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Canterbury, University of (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Chemical Heritage Foundation (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Chen, Y.T. (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Coherent Laser Group (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Continetti, Robert E. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - D (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - DeBakey, Michael E. (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - E (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - F (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Fei Binhai (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - G (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Gillis, Malcolm (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Graduate University for Advanced Studies (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - H (Box 15, Folder 30-31)
    - Halas, Naomi J. (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Heath, James R. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - I (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - J (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Kironde, Sanyu (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Kroto, Harry (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - L (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - M (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Mantsch, Henry M. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Miller, Charles (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - N (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - National Academy of Sciences (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - National Institute of Standards Technology (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - O (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Ohio State University (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Oxford University (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - P (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Paretchan, Harold R. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Pitzer, Kenneth (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - R (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - S (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Scott, Graham (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Smalley, Richard (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Smolka, Klaus-Peter (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - T (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Tittel, Frank K. (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - U (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - W (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Weizmann Institute of Science (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Welch Foundation (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Elie Wiesel Foundation (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Y (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Subseries B: Office files
    - Alumni College (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Awards and Honors (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Bremen International University (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Committees (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, General (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, National Academy of Science (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Requests for Autographs (Box 17, Folder 7-9)
    - Faculty related (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Retreat, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Joe L. Franklin Lectures (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Invitations for Presentations (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Lectures (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Nobel Prize related (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Nobel Prize related Events (Box 17, Folder 16-17)
    - Nobel Prize, Clock (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Nobel Prize generated Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Nobel Prize, Congratulatory Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Nobel Prize, National Science Foundation trip (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Nobel Prize Publicity (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Nobel Prize, Stockholm Trip (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Rice Quantum Institute (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Smalley, Richard E. (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Digital files from hard drive, 1991-2005
  - Subseries C: Memorabilia
    - Patch; National Space Biomedical Research Institute, 2012 (Box 18)
    - Plaque: Presented to Dr. Robert F. Curl in appreciation for your distinguished presence at the 47th Alamo Regional Science & Engineering Fair, March 22, 2003 (Box 18)
    - Medal: Gobierno de la Ciudad de Buenos Aires; al Doctor D. Robert F. Curl premio Nobel de Quimica 1996 "VIsitante ilustre de la Ciudad de Buenos Aires" (Box 18)
    - Medal: Spectroscopica Marcus Marci Societas Promeritis de Spectroscopla 1998 R.F. Curl, Jr., Praha (Box 18)
    - St. Mary's University [Nova Scotia] Lin Great Speakers Series; Robert Curl (Box 18)
    - Plaque: The SMU Chapter of Sigma Xi The Scientific Research Society presented to Robert Curl, Ph. D. in appreication for his service and dedication to Science, May 1997 (Box 18)
    - Medal: Lindau Tagungen der NobelPreistrager (Box 18)
    - Certificate: USTC cordially invites Dr. Robert F. Curl as Honorary Professor. President, University of Science and Technology of China, May 15, 2002 (Box 18)
    - Invitation, program, newspaper, CD and regalia: 10eme anniersaire Universite du Littoral Cote d'Opale Seance Solennelle de Remise de Diplomes de Docteur Honoris Causa, 2002 (Box 18)
    - Platter: Special Lecture Indian Institute of Chemical Technology; Professor Robert F. Crul, 1998 Nobel Laureate in Chemistry, Rice University, Houston, USA; 31 Dec. 2007 (Box 18)
    - Photographs: visit to the National Institute of Advanced Interdisciplinary Research, Tsukuba, Japan, 1998 (Box 18)
    - Plaque: Nankai University guest professorship is hereby conferred upon Dr. Robert F. Curl in recognition of his honour and achievement and in acknowledgement of the esteem of Nankai University; Professor Gong Ke, President April 17, 2012 (Box 19)
    - Framed medal and plaque: Exemplary Achivevement in Science; Dr. Robert Curl, Chemistry; Texas Science Hall of Fame Charter Member, Jan. 17, 2000 (Box 19)
    - Buckyball stamps from UK (Box 19)
    - Phi Beta Kappa certificate, 1953-12-04 (Box 19)
    - Certificate: Presented to Nobel Laureate Dr. Robert F. Curl, Jr. for serving as the inaugural speaker for the Putcha Venkateskarlu Memorial Lecture Series at Alabama A&M University, Huntsville, AL, Oct. 23, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Certificate: Spektroskopicka Spolecnost Jana Marca Marci udeluje Medaili Jana Marca Marci Z Kronlandu F.R. Curl, Jr. za vynikajici vedecke uspechy v oborus, 24.8.1998 (Box 19)
    - Photographs: Texas Science Hall of Fame Charter Members visit to the Texas State Capitol, Tues., Jan. 16, 2001 (Box 19)
    - Senate of the State of Texas Senate Resolution No. 7 re: charter inductees of the Texas Science Hall of Fame, 2001-01-16 (Box 19)
    - Certificate: Royal Society of Chemistry Centenary Lectureship awarded to Robert Floyd Curl for 1998/99, 1999-05 (Box 19)
    - Certificate: Optical Society of America in recognition of distinguished service in the advancement of optics, Robert Curl has been elected a fellow of the Optical Society of America, in testimony whereof, the President and Executive Director have hereon set their hands and the seal of the Society this twelfth day of Sept., 1995, 1995-09-12 (Box 19)
    - Certificate: The National Space Biomedical Research Institute and the Baylor College of Medicine Center for Space Medicine recognizes Robert F. Curl Jr., Ph.D. for delivering the inaugural presentation in the Consolidated Research Facility Distinguished Lecture Series, 2012-12-19 (Box 19)
    - Certificate: Prof. Robert F. Curl is hereby conferred the title of Honorary Professor by East China University of Science and Technology, 2007 (Box 19)
    - Certificate: Der Forschungspreis Chemie 2004 der Ruhr-Universitat Bochum gestiftet vom Arbeitgegerverhand Chemie. Westfallen wird verliehen an Prof. Dr.Robert F. Curl, Chemistry Dept. and Rice Quantum Institute, Rice Univ., Houston, TX USA, 2004-05-27 (Box 19)
    - Certificate of Appreciation presented to Dr. Robert F. Curl in appreciation of his dedication to the Mu Alpha Theta Math Club Honor Society and the AP Math and Science Program at Thomas Jefferson High School, San Antonio, TX, 2000-04-03 (Box 19)
    - Certificate: The Madison Marshall Award 1998 North Alabama Section of the American Chemical Society presented to Robert F. Curl, Jr. Nobel Laureate for outstanding contributions to chemistry, 1998-10-03 (Box 19)
    - House Journal Proceedings for Jan. 16, 2001 [lists Dr. Robert T. Curl, Nobel Laureate in chemistry], 2001-01-16 (Box 19)
    - Senate Journal Proceedings for Jan. 16, 2001 [lists Texas Science Hall of Fame members], 2001-01-16 (Box 19)
    - Photo: Twenty-Seventh International Symposium on Free Radicals, Taipei, Taiwan, 2004-07-25-2004-07-30 (Box 19)
    - Plaque: Distinguished Texas Scientist Robert F. Crul, 1997 (Box 19)
    - Poster: Arts Council of Brazos Valley 2001 Distinguished Lecture Series "An Adventure in Science" Speaker, Robert F. Curl, PH.D. 1996 Nobel Laureate in Chemistry, 2001-02-06 (Box 20)
    - Certificate: Xiamen University respectfully confers the honor of Professor upon Dr. Robert Floyd Curl (Box 20)
    - Certificate: Republique Francaise Universite du Littoral Cote d'Opale conferons a Monsieur Robert F. Curl Jr. le titre de Docteur Honoris Causa de l'Universite du Littoral Cote d'Opale, 2002-11-29 (Box 20)
    - Certificate: Bar-Ilan University, Ramal Gan, Israel, through the powers vested by the University Senate and Board of Trustees confer the degree of Doctor of Philosophy, Honoris Causa upon Professor Robert Floyd Curl, 2010-05-11 (Box 20)
    - Universidad de Buenos Aires ha resuelto conferir Honoris Causa el titulo de Doctor de la Univesidad al Doctor Robert L. Curl, 1997-05-02 (Box 20)
    - Certificate: Robert F. Curl has been duly elected a member of the National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America, 1997-04-29 (Box 20)
    - Plate and plaque: "The Golden Plate" awarded to America's captains of achievement 'representing the many who excel" in the great fields of endeavor; Thirty-Sixth Annual Banquet of the Golden Plate, Baltimore, MD, 1997-05-22 (Box 20)
    - Certificate: Texas Senate Proclamation No. 1900 (Rodney Ellis) The Senate of the State of Texas hereby congratulates Dr. Robert F. Curl on receiving the Nobel Prize for Chemistry (Box 20)
    - Rice University Distinguished Alumni Award, framed, 1997 (Oversize 23)
      General
      The framed award is in the annex slot 23
- Series XII: Correspondence, 2005-2008
  - Friends of Israeli-Palestinian Science Organization Meeting (IPSO)
    - IPSO Meeting, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - IPSO Meeting, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - IPSO Meeting, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - IPSO Meeting, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Grant Proposals, 1996, 2001
    - Grant Proposal, NSF, with Supporting Documents (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Grant Proposal, NSF, with Supporting Documents (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Grant Proposal, ARP/ATP, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Research Publications, 1955-2011
    - Volumetric and Thermodynamic Properties of Fluids, I and II, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Volumetric and Thermodynamic Properties of Fluids, III, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Thermodynamic Properties of Normal Fluids, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Spectrum and Structure of Disiloxane, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Microwave Spectrum, Barrier to Internal Rotation and Structure of Methyl Formate, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Calculation of Interaction Matrix Elements for Asymmetric Rotors..., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Chlorine Dioxide, IV, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Chlorine Dioxide, V, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Infrared Spectrum of N-Methylenemethylamine, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Relationship between Electron Spin Rotation Coupling Constants..., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Microwave Spectrum and Force Constants of SiF2: Centrifugal Distortion, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 18)